[theme music playing]
I have a feeling she's suspicious of you.
She could be planning something.
I'll send my men there to abduct Ivy
and bring her to my happy place.
[Arnaldo] I trust her, Grandpa.
She'd never betray me.
Have you committed murder because of love?
Grandpa taught me to use my brain
over my emotions.
If you let emotion take over,
you might end up killing someone.
[Ivy] Your death isn't payment enough
for what you did.
I won't let you off that easily, Arnaldo.
I won't taint my hands
with blood for someone like you.
[Raul] Right now, I'm in
control of the situation.
So, I can provide everything you need.
But you have to give me what I need too.
We must rise above our fears!
They cannot oppress us if we are united!
Long live the new Ardiente!
[all] Long live!
[applause]
It's from a certain Jaguar.
They want to enter the gambling scene
here in Ardiente.
[Julio] Kittens aren't welcome
in my business.
[gunshot]
Tell the congressman
that the Jaguar is here.
And he will rule Poblacion Ardiente.
[Diego] Ivy, I just want to
make sure you're safe.
I won't do anything that'll get me killed.
I can protect myself.
[Diego] If you need me,
you know where to find me.
I'm done playing your games.
-Arnaldo, wait!
-What?! Explain yourself!
Listen to me.
Give me one good reason
why I need to stay!
I love you.
Stay, Arnaldo. I love you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[knocks on door]
Come in.
Excuse me, Congressman.
[suspenseful music playing]
Honorable Congressman,
Sorry about killing your men,
but they were getting too cocky.
That's why I'm advising you
to have some coffee.
Because if I find you
getting too cocky as well,
I'll put a bullet through your head.
Love, Jaguar.
[suspenseful music playing]
Okay, I'll admit.
I admit that…
Diego and I still see each other.
But I told him to stay away.
Because I know I'm sure of…
my feelings for you.
I'm testing the depth
of your feelings for me.
Arnaldo, I'm not playing you.
I'm not toying with you.
I love you, and I hope…
I hope that's enough for you to stay.
I love you.
I love you, Arnaldo.
[tense music playing]
It's more than enough.
More than enough reason.
[tense music playing]
I've been loving you for so long.
[exhales]
Arnaldo…
[Arnaldo] Ouch!
-Does it hurt?
-Please be gentle.
It hurts.
Sorry.
You're so cute, you know?
You're way cuter.
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
-Arnaldo…
But seriously, thank you
for taking care of me.
I love you.
[phone ringing]
-[phone ringing]
-[Arnaldo groans]
-Bad timing.
-[phone ringing]
Sorry, I have to take this. It's Grandpa.
-Hello, Grandpa?
-Arnaldo.
Come home right now.
Huh? But why?
Somebody new picked a fight
with our family.
[ominous music playing]
Leave everything right there. Thank you.
You're welcome, ma'am.
We'll return to our posts now.
Okay. Have some snacks too.
Thank you, ma'am.
Um, Nimfa?
Leave everything here. You can go home.
Your parents might be looking for you.
Oh, it's okay, Miss Camia.
You see, my father isn't around.
He's in Manila.
Besides, I'm sure he'll be happy
once he finds out
that I'm helping the bravest
opponent of the Ardientes.
[Nimfa chuckles]
Where's your mother?
[sighs] She's gone.
Um… Miss Camia?
Don't you have any helpers around?
They took the day off.
I see.
Wait, so who does the chores for you?
No one.
I grew up poor.
I can do everything on my own.
But you have so many things to do.
You might overwork yourself.
All right, then.
I'll do the household chores myself.
I can do everything! All around!
Don't worry, you don't have to pay me.
-Goodness.
-I'll be your volunteer helper.
Nimfa, you don't have to.
But, Miss Camia, that's what I want to do.
Come on, let me do it.
Please?
No.
[sighs]
-[Camia chuckles]
-[phone ringing]
Hold on. I have to answer this.
-Okay, ma'am.
-[phone ringing]
Hello?
Lily.
You're going home already?
But why?
Okay, dear. Stay safe
on your way home, okay?
Okay. Bye.
[unsettling music playing]
["Wildflower" by Arnel Pineda playing]
♪ She's faced the hardest times
You can imagine ♪
♪ And many times
Her eyes fought back the tears ♪
♪ And when her youthful world
Was about to fall in ♪
♪ Each time her slender shoulders
Bore the weight of all her fears… ♪
You'll always be in my heart,
Nanny Carlotta.
I'll continue our fight.
I'll find justice for your death.
♪ Let her cry ♪
♪ For she's a lady ♪
♪ Let her dream ♪
♪ She's a child ♪
♪ Let the rain… ♪
Nanny Carlotta. I've laid down the trap.
All we need is for him
to walk right into it.
[Carlotta] Jepoy is gone.
No one else is going to protect you.
[Diego] I will.
I'll protect Ivy.
[Diego] Ivy, I just want to
make sure you're safe.
[Ivy] I won't do anything
that'll get me killed.
I can protect myself.
If you need me, you know where to find me.
Ivy, be careful.
♪ Be careful how you touch her
For she'll awaken ♪
♪ And sleep's the only freedom
That she knows ♪
♪ And when you walk into her eyes
You won't believe ♪
♪ The way she's always paying
For a debt she never owes ♪
[suspenseful music playing]
Jaguar!
[Jaguar] There's more
where that came from.
We'll take all of the Ardientes' money.
We'll milk them dry.
[goon] For the Jaguar!
[goons] Jaguar!
Oh, Miss Camia!
Nimfa, what are you doing here?
I brought you some lunch
so that you wouldn't have to cook.
Here, I have some vegetables and fish.
I'm sorry, that's all I've got…
It's all I can afford.
Nimfa, you shouldn't have!
You don't have to do this.
[chuckles]
Well, I like being thoughtful to you.
But, what if tell you to
stop being thoughtful?
Will you stop?
Hmm…
No, ma'am.
I really want to work
as your house helper.
What?
Please, Miss Camia let me work for you.
-Oh, Nimfa.
-Please.
-Nimfa, get up!
-Let me work for you.
Oh, Nimfa…
Why are you doing this?
[sighs]
Because…
I see my mother in you.
[soft music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
[Rufo] Hello, boss?
Okay.
Jaguar, the boss wants to talk to you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
Papa, you wanted to see us?
Yes, sit down.
I want everyone here listening.
Including me, Papa?
I'm not in a joking mood, Raul.
Sit down and listen.
[tense music playing]
[heavy sigh]
-Good morning, Grandpa.
-You're late.
What happened to your neck?
This? Nothing, I'm okay.
So, we're all here.
-What's this meeting for?
-Sit down.
An armed group of men
broke into our gambling den.
They took over our operations,
they took our money,
and they killed our people.
And the leader of this
group calls himself…
Jaguar.
Jaguar?
[Julio sighs]
[tense music playing]
HOW'S MY HANDSOME MAYOR?
I MISS YOU!
[Julio] Now, listen.
I have had many encounters
and many threats in my political career.
But, I'm telling you,
this group is different.
This group is dangerous.
They're fearless.
They have weapons, they--
Arnaldo, are you listening to me?
-Oh--
-Put that phone down!
Yes.
I want you to focus on this enemy!
Use your informants! Use
your people! Spread the word!
I'm willing to give
10 million pesos as a reward
to whoever can tell me
who and where that Jaguar is.
[tense music playing]
Please, Miss Camia!
I'll be the happiest
if you let me work for you.
So, please… Let me!
Please!
-Please, ma'am!
-[Camia chuckles]
Please say yes!
Please, ma'am!
All right.
But you can't live here.
You have to head home.
Yes, I promise!
And you'll follow every security rule.
I will! Thank you, Miss Camia!
-Thank you so much.
-Okay, you're hired.
You can start right now.
-Thank you so much.
-You're welcome.
-[phone ringing]
-Sorry, Miss Camia.
I have to take this call.
-It might be my dad.
-Okay, take the call.
Come find me when you're done.
-Okay.
-All right.
-Thanks again, Miss Camia.
-No problem.
-Thank you!
-[phone ringing]
[sighs]
[heavy breathing]
[ominous music playing]
Hello.
Yes.
I'm inside the house.
All right.
[ominous music playing]
This is what I've always feared.
I don't understand
why you're threatened by Jaguar.
He doesn't even have the balls
to show his face.
I'm not talking about the Jaguar!
You, Arnaldo!
You've lost focus on your mission
to be the heir to this family's throne.
And all because of that woman!
"That woman." "That woman."
Here we go again.
Grandpa…
My whole life I've served this family.
Since the start, I've done nothing
but try to win your approval.
Just this once, let me be happy.
And I'll prove to you
that I'll be a better man because of her.
Don't say it.
Do it!
Ivy Aguas is only an asset to this family
because of her money.
And she becomes a problem
when you let your stupid heart
get ahead of you!
And that makes you selfish!
What do you want me to do?
Tell me.
You really want her that bad?
Then you go out there and get her!
But make sure
that the whole family
benefits from her assets and money.
What is hers should be ours!
And what is ours
will never be hers.
Do you understand what I'm saying?!
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Yes, Mr. Mayor?
I was just thinking about you.
I want to see you.
I have something important to say.
Sure.
Just tell me where and when,
and I'll be there.
[ominous music playing]
Miss Aguas…
Welcome to my playground.
Is that why you brought me here?
You want to play around, Mr. Mayor?
Well…
I'd like to see how good your shot is.
Have you forgotten?
I already showed you how good I am.
[gunshots]
[sultry music playing]
Yes, you're good.
You're good at making lucky shots.
Lucky shots? Really?
Okay, then. Prove me wrong.
Prove to me you belong in my world.
Whoever hits all targets in
the shortest amount of time…
wins.
And what's the prize?
It's a surprise.
Here you go.
[tense music playing]
Ready?
Ready?!
Go.
-[action music playing]
-[gunshots]
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[unsettling music playing]
[Arnaldo clapping]
Congratulations, Ivy.
You won.
And this…
This is your prize.
A lifetime of love and happiness…
with me.
[unsettling music playing]
Ivy Aguas…
I love you.
Will you marry me?
[tense music playing]
"No" isn't an option?
You should know by now
I don't take "no" for an answer.
[tense music playing]
Yes.
Yes, Arnaldo. I will marry you.
Yes, Arnaldo.
Your hand, please?
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
How will I bring the Ardientes down?
Step one: make their favorite
grandson fall for me,
and use him against them.
[fake chuckles]
Arnaldo…
Yes!
-[Ivy forces a laugh]
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
Whoo!
I'm so lucky. Thank you.
Thank you very much for saying yes.
Don't sound so cocky.
You never know.
This?
You've already seen
how good I am at shooting.
Well, don't worry, hon.
I love challenges.
Wait, "hon"?
What's wrong?
From now on, that will be
our term of endearment.
My fiancé is so lame.
Well, you can't blame a man in love.
So, I'm okay with it.
Anyway, I can't wait
to tell this to my family.
I'm sure they'll be happy for us.
I'll set a dinner
to announce this to everyone.
You know, Emilia?
Your dad surprised me.
I've known him for a long time,
but this is the first time I've heard him
put a 10-million bounty
on an enemy's head.
It's a huge amount of money.
Well, it only goes to show
he's not taking things lightly.
Do you think he's afraid of the Jaguar?
It's possible.
So your dad does know fear.
I'm curious, Raul.
You seem happy knowing
that Papa is stressed.
No, um…
The truth is, I'm happy for you
because an opportunity came for you.
I know you're good.
And that only you can kill the Jaguar.
You're a sweet-talker, huh?
[chuckles]
You know, as much as
I want to help Papa now,
I have so much on my plate already.
Like what?
Our marriage.
Can't I prioritize my love life
for a change?
[tense music playing]
You know, Emilia?
That's the greatest thing
I've heard today.
What you just said.
-Really, Raul?
-Mm-hm.
[tense music playing]
Emilia.
I'd love to marry you again.
[giggles]
Yes, Raul!
-You sure?
-Yes!
-[Raul chuckles]
I'll marry you again! Over and over.
I'll marry you.
[Ivy] Yes, everyone will be happy,
except your mom.
It doesn't matter.
No one cares for her anymore.
So, if I ask you to choose
between me and Emilia,
you'll choose your fiancée?
Isn't it obvious?
My fiancé is so sweet.
-[Arnaldo snickers]
-Come here, hon.
Mmm!
Aww.
-I'm so lucky to have you.
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
[Arnaldo sighs]
Finally.
You're all mine.
I'm all yours.
Hmm…
[tense music playing]
Are you happy?
[sighs]
I love you.
Say it again.
I love you so much.
Again.
I love you. I love you, Ivy Aguas!
I love you!
I can't hear you.
I love you, Ivy Aguas!
-Aww, Arnaldo.
-[chuckles]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
It's Diego.
Hey.
Diego. You're here.
-Uncle. Nanny.
-Hey…
I thought you were…
going to watch over Ivy?
We talked already.
She promised me
she won't do anything dangerous.
And I need to trust her.
That's right.
So that you can focus on other things.
[Pandoy] The carpenters said…
it'll cost us 20,000 pesos
to fix our cooperative.
How much do we have in our funds now?
It's only 15,000 for now.
[Pandoy] Diego, I think…
we should find a new place
to set up your campaign headquarters.
No, Uncle.
We'll have this cooperative fixed.
We have to do it not just for my campaign,
but for the farmers as well.
But, Diego, we don't have enough manpower,
we don't have the means,
and we lack funds for your campaign.
Who can help us?
I've got someone in mind.
Excuse me.
[suspenseful music playing]
[dark music playing]
Jaguar.
The boss is here.
[dark music playing]
[phone ringing]
Ma'am, I'm here now.
[ominous music playing]
All right.
[suspenseful music playing]
Mr. Jaguar?
That's a pretty cool name.
Did you…
miss me?
[suspenseful music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
Nimfa, I want you to tell me
everything you know about Camia Cruz.
All right, ma'am.
[suspenseful music playing]
Be careful! Oh, dear.
It's not like we'll finish!
We don't have the materials
or the manpower.
I can do this, Nanny. Don't worry.
Where's the help you said was coming?
I'm sure he's on his way.
Who's coming again?
Just wait, Nanny. You'll find out later.
[Pandoy] But, where's your friend?
Are you sure he's still coming?
[Diego] Don't worry. He'll be here.
-Oh!
-What is it?
He's here!
[Loring] Oh!
[man] I thought he wasn't
going to show up!
[Pandoy] Looks like people are coming in.
[Loring] Oh…
Is… Is that him?
-Diego!
-Hey!
-Batch!
-Oh, it's Batch!
-Batch?
-[chuckling]
-Yes, it's him!
-It is Batch!
Hey!
How have you been, bro?
Thanks for doing this.
We really need your help.
Anything for you!
[Diego] Nanny, Uncle…
-He's Batch.
-Yes.
This is my best friend from college,
Marlon Espina.
-Hi, I'm Marlon Espina.
-Oh, Marlon?
-Is that your real name?
-Yes.
-I'm sorry.
-Not Batch.
Well, we're batch mates.
-Yes.
-[Pandoy chuckles]
I'm here to help out
with Diego's campaign too.
Thank you, Marlon!
That's great!
Your timing's perfect!
Too bad we're short
on raw materials and manpower.
And you're alone. How are we doing this?
You don't have to worry about that.
Diego's caught me up on all the problems,
so I brought some people over.
-Oh!
-Wow!
That's a lot!
-There they are!
-Materials too?
[Marlon] Yes.
-All of those?
-Yes, sir!
It's nothing.
Thank you!
-What are best friends for?
-That's very helpful!
Everybody!
The materials are here!
-Here they come.
-Whoa!
-These are a lot!
-Thank you, Marlon!
[Pandoy] You can put those over there!
Thank you. Over there.
-Over here.
-Can you lift that up?
-Batch, this'll help us a lot.
-Are there more?
We really have to fix this up.
-Let's help them.
-Go!
Are there more?
Come on!
-Are there more?
-Let's go help them.
[Loring] You helped us out
a lot. Thank you.
How is Camia's new house helper doing?
I think I've earned her trust.
I even call her Miss Camia now.
Are you sure about that?
What if she's just leading you on?
I'd bet my life on it!
Well, you know
what's at stake here, right?
An ambitious woman like you
won't pass up an opportunity like this.
[tense music playing]
-You're coming with us!
-Where are you taking me?
-Get your hands off me!
-Get in!
Let me go!
Let go!
Get your hands off me!
Let me go!
[Nimfa panting]
Governor?
You're Nimfa, right?
I'm not going to hurt you…
if you do everything as I say.
Let's discuss your bright future.
You can shove that bright future…
down your throat!
-[Emilia chuckles]
-Hey!
-Let go!
-Oops.
Let go of me!
[Nimfa sobbing]
Please don't make this difficult for me!
You know what could happen
if you refuse to help me, right?
[sobbing]
[tense music playing]
I'll give you this house and lot…
if you do exactly as I say.
And you see that car outside?
You can have that for free too.
And that's not all…
I'll also give you all the money
you could ever want.
[Claire] Just think of it as a bonus…
As long as the Ardientes are in power,
they'll support you.
How can I be sure you won't just kill me?
Why?
Do I look like a murderer to you?
Yes.
[Nimfa whimpers]
Emilia.
[Emilia hisses, sighs]
Don't make this complicated, Nimfa.
I can guarantee you,
you'll be able to provide
for your father after this.
[Emilia] I will lift you out of poverty.
I'll make you a very rich woman.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia sighs]
Fine.
I'll do it.
But, on one condition.
You won't just give me the house…
The car…
And the money…
What else do you want?
Diego.
I want Diego to be mine after all this.
And you'll help me make that happen.
[scoffs]
I'm really starting to like you.
Because of that, you're getting a bonus.
You get to stay here
for a night, for free.
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm going to be rich.
This is the life!
[sighs]
This place is awesome!
And the mattress is so soft!
[sighs]
[gasps]
Wow!
[dark music playing]
Ma'am…
I'm sorry.
You look prettier now that you're rich.
[clears throat]
But all this will go to waste…
if you end up failing me.
I have a very short temper.
Um… [nervous laugh]
Ma'am, I'll do my best.
Don't worry.
-[Nimfa] Dad, take care, okay?
-[Fernan] I will.
[Nimfa] I'll just follow you there.
And it's good that you're going away.
The elections are coming up.
You might have another encounter
with the Ardientes.
[Fernan chuckles]
Why don't you come with me, dear?
Dad, I need to help Diego
with his campaign.
I have a bad feeling about this.
[chuckles] You're so dramatic, Dad.
You better get going.
Stop making the nice driver wait.
Go on.
The next time we see
each other again, Dad,
I'll make sure we have a much better life.
Don't worry, Governor.
We'll learn all of Camia Cruz's secrets.
Even who her backer is.
Nimfa, I already know it's Ivy Aguas.
I just need to find concrete proof,
so I can finally take that woman down.
[tense music playing]
[burps]
[Diego] Yes.
We'll need all the volunteers we can get.
Thank you, Marlon.
I knew I could count on you.
Bye.
[pensive music playing]
Our dreams are slowly coming true, Ivy.
I can finally help this town move forward.
I can finally provide its people
with the life they deserve.
A new Ardiente.
[Arnaldo] Hon…
Hon, I can't wait to be with you 24/7.
-[Ivy sighs]
-I want to marry you soon.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Hon, you're getting too excited.
You should make me miss you a little.
I might end up getting sick of you.
[scoffs]
Goodnight, hon.
Goodnight. I love you.
I love you too.
[tense music playing]
Bye.
No.
This can't be true.
[tense music playing]
You really fell for my trap, my fiancé.
Ivy!
Diego?
How'd you find out I moved here?
Did I hear that right?
Are you going to marry Arnaldo?
Tell me it isn't true.
[tense music playing]
Yes.
It's true.
[sullen music playing]
No.
I won't let you.
Ivy, why did it have to come to this?
You're going to marry the man
who might've killed Nanny Carlotta?
[sullen music playing]
[Ivy sighs deeply]
Listen, Diego, I've made my decision.
And not even you can change it.
I just want you to know
this is the last night
we'll ever see each other.
We can't keep seeing each other, Diego.
Because I don't want to ruin
my relationship with Arnaldo
because of you.
I hope you understand.
[sullen music playing]
Ivy!
I know what you're doing.
You're pushing me away.
But I know. I can feel it.
Your relationship with Arnaldo isn't true.
You're just using him because
you want to seek revenge.
No.
No, you're lying.
You don't have to do this alone.
I'm here. Your mother's here.
And I found Mr. Arthur.
He can testify for us.
I can testify too, so we can
bring down the Ardientes.
Diego, I want to fight them on my own.
Too many people have gotten hurt.
Too many have died.
Who's next? You?
After Jepoy and Nanny Carlotta,
you're going to die too?
I won't allow those evil Ardientes
to kill one more person!
I'm ready to kill for you,
just to stop you
from ending up with Arnaldo.
It's simple, Diego!
It's so simple!
You just have to understand!
I'm sorry, Ivy, but I'll do everything
to stop you from marrying Arnaldo!
I'm sorry.
I just love you too much.
[somber music playing]
Nimfa?
Where did you go?
Um…
I just stepped out to call my father.
Why did you have to step out
to make a call?
You're allowed to talk to your father
inside the house.
Nimfa?
Is there something you're not telling me?
[tense music playing]
Are you hiding something?
No, ma'am.
I'm sorry for not asking permission.
[sighs] All I'm saying is…
We need to be careful.
Especially since you know
the Ardientes are watching us.
Yes, I understand.
Okay.
Just finish your chores for today.
When you're done, you can head home.
Yes, ma'am.
[suspenseful music playing]
[echoing thud]
[tense music playing]
[heavy breathing]
-[panting]
-[metal chains clanking]
[tense music playing]
[panting, huffing]
[grunting]
[loud thud]
[screaming]
[panting]
[labored breathing]
[Ivy] I've made my decision.
And not even you can change it.
This is the last night
we'll ever see each other.
I don't want to ruin
my relationship with Arnaldo
because of you.
[panting]
[huffs]
[Diego] You're going to marry the man
who might've killed Nanny Carlotta?
You don't have to do this alone.
I'm here.
I'm ready to kill for you,
just to stop you
from ending up with Arnaldo.
I'm sorry. I just love you too much.
[panting]
["Nanghihinayang"
by Angeline Quinto playing]
[panting]
["Nanghihinayang"
by Angeline Quinto playing]
[rock music playing]
[Ivy] A wounded enemy
comes back even stronger.
[Julio] I am still the ruler
of Poblacion Ardiente.
[Emilia] You'll all go crazy for my love.
[sinister laughter]
[Camia] Now's the time to take my revenge.
[Raul] I'll never let go of
what should be mine.
[Jepoy] They can never silence me.
[Arnaldo] I will get everything I want.
[Diego] I'm done being blind.
-I am done being an Ardiente.
-[screaming]
-[glass breaking]
-[rock music playing]